<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>general on University of Michigan Fencing Club</title><link>https://um-fencing.github.io/categories/general/</link><description>Recent content in general on University of Michigan Fencing Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>(c) 2022 University of Michigan Fencing Club</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:49:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://um-fencing.github.io/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Donate</title><link>https://um-fencing.github.io/donate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:49:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://um-fencing.github.io/donate/</guid><description>The University of Michigan Fencing Club is excited about the upcoming season. We are not only eager to defend our title as the USACFC national champions, but we want everyone on campus to have the opportunity to join our club, learn how to fence, and take fencing with them for the rest of their lives.
One of our top priorities is investing in the future to create a growing and sustainable organization.</description></item><item><title>About Fencing</title><link>https://um-fencing.github.io/about_fencing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:07:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://um-fencing.github.io/about_fencing/</guid><description>The sport of fencing has three weapons: foil, epee and saber. The object of a fencing bout (what an individual &amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; is called) is to land a specified number of touches on your opponent before he/she scores that number on you. Each bout is officiated by a referee called a director.
Electric Scoring All official tournaments are conducted using electric scoring systems. The fencers connect themselves, their blades, and their metal jackets (lames) to a retractable cord (reel), which plugs in to a scoring machine (pictured left).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://um-fencing.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 15:09:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://um-fencing.github.io/contact/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you! If you have a question, you can ask any of our officers at practice or contact us electronically.
Have general inquiry questions? Email us at fencingofficers@umich.edu. We can help in person, too. Stop by during any practice and we&amp;rsquo;ll take care of you.
Want to anonymously give feedback, ask a question, raise a concern, etc.? Please use our suggestions box.
Officers Position Name Email Address Contact About Co-President Molly Cavanaugh mojocav@umich.</description></item><item><title>Roster</title><link>https://um-fencing.github.io/roster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://um-fencing.github.io/roster/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s Team Name Weapon Year Hometown Zachary Brooks Epee Grad Shawnee, KS Ian Chu Epee FR Bozeman, MT Maximilian Coolidge Crouthamel Epee SR Grand Rapids, MI Kyle Garcia-Rogers Epee FR North Reading, MA Edmond Han (Captain) Epee SR Johns Creek, GA Jiawei He Epee JR Guangdong, China Noah Jacobs Epee JR Fruitport, MI Sterling Kim Epee FR Los Angeles, CA Roland Kwok Epee Non-Student Ann Arbor, MI Tianyu Liang Epee SO Guangzhou, China Daniel Lyons Epee SR Paw Paw, MI Ansh Mehta Epee FR Dubai, UAE Sanil Mittal Epee FR New Delhi, India Ryan Moon Epee FR Johns Creek, GA Armando Otero Epee SR San Juan, Puerto Rico Brandon Nguyen Epee Grad Austin, TX Ibrahim Musaddequr Rahman Epee FR Morgantown, WV Zachary Tiplady Epee SO Canton, MI Greg Tomaszycki Epee Non-Student Ann Arbor, MI Rohan Valluri Epee SR Ashburn, VA Maxmillian Wiegel Epee SO Grosse Pointe Woods, MI Colin Yoon Epee JR San Francisco, CA Caedon Zube Epee FR Middleville, MI Brandon Battle Foil SR Detroit, MI Atticus Driver Foil SO Yuba City, CA Eli Goldweber Foil Grad Cincinnati, OH Keith Haw (Captain) Foil SO Pittsburgh, PA Hugo He Foil JR China James Kennedy Foil JR Oak Park, IL Gordon Ng Foil FR Southgate, MI Alvin Poon Foil SO Toronto, Canada Aaron Renberg Foil Grad Bethesda, MD Cameron Rifkin Foil JR Birmingham, MI Arun Rushton Foil FR Novi, MI Peter Ryner Foil SR Harbor Springs, MI Ryder Spees Foil FR Fenton, MI Santiago Suarez Foil SR Madrid, Spain Anthony Vanlian Foil FR Battle Creek, MI Aaron Maxwell Belman-Wells Saber FR Ann Arbor, MI Thomas Choi Saber JR Lake Orion, MI Joshua Cooper Saber Grad Detroit, MI Zain Dhanani Saber FR Palo Alto, CA Jake Huang Saber JR China Maxwell Iseler Saber FR Port Hope, MI Luke Kurfess Saber JR Horton, MI Peter Murray (Captain) Saber SR Highland Park, IL Sean Richards Saber SO Canton, MI James Utley Saber JR Canton, MI Jonathan Wang Saber FR Troy, MI Qifa Wang Saber SO Lexington, MA Nate White Saber SO Concord, MA Corey Zhou Saber SO Shanghai, China Women&amp;rsquo;s Team Name Weapon Year Hometown Faith Chang (Captain) Epee SR San Jose, CA Sohee Chung Epee SO Seoul, South Korea Jingqi Fan Epee JR Las Vegas, NV Annmarie Guarink Epee FR Dearborn, MI Emeline Hanna Epee SO Alpena, MI Sookyung Heo Epee JR Seoul, South Korea Diana Huang Epee SR Solon, OH Kai Huie Epee SO New York, NY Hilary Lam Epee SO Bloomfield Hills, MI Brianna Moglianesi Epee JR Warren, NJ Sarah Rahman Epee JR Miami, FL Rebecca Saladin Epee FR Dearborn, MI Amina Troupe (Captain) Epee SR Montclair, NJ Jasmine An Foil Grad Ann Arbor, MI Molly Cavanaugh (Captain) Foil SR Okemos, MI Hanna Chen Foil SO Pittsburgh, PA Alifa Chowdhury Foil FR Ontario, Canada Isabelle DeGaynor Foil SO Bloomfield Hills, MI Ryan Ettner Foil FR Culver City, CA Rachel Hendrian Foil SO Farmington Hills, MI Mackenzie Hubbard Foil SR Ludington, MI Saima Jamal Foil JR Teaneck, NJ Azaria Knight Foil JR Southfield, MI Jennifer Meng Foil FR Ann Arbor, MI Jin Niu Foil JR Beijing, China Sunskriti Paranjape Foil JR Portland, OR Sandhya Srinivasan Foil JR Troy, MI Dominika Urbaniak Foil FR Hamtramck, MI Lahari Vavilala Foil JR Novi, MI Lucy Wang Foil JR Rockville, MD Tina Yu Foil FR Taiwan Alanna Carlo-Pagan Saber FR San Juan, Puerto Rico Emely Hernandez Saber SR Ontario, Canada Sam Jiao Saber Grad Beijing, China Margaret Koberstein (Captain) Saber SO Libertyville, IL Alicja Maria Krasowska Saber FR Warsaw, Poland Emerson Lauster Saber FR Gaylord, MI Henriette Lucas Saber JR Novi, MI Nicolette Lukibanova Saber SO Rochester, MI Claire Maiocco Saber Grad Winter Park, FL Petra Mihalko Saber FR Grosse Ile, MI Lex Pacifico Saber FR Ann Arbor, MI Lauren Peng Saber JR Shanghai, China Tejaswini Srinivas Reddy Saber JR Midland, MI Agamjot Sangotra Saber Grad Montgomery, NJ Michelle Wu Saber SO Ridgewood, NJ Yimeng Zhang Saber FR Wuhan, China Coaches Name Position Jim Vesper Head Coach Kevin Oh Volunteer Assistant Coach Andrew Aitken Volunteer Assistant Coach Jason Goodman Volunteer Assistant Cocah Cary Huang Volunteer Assistant Coach</description></item></channel></rss>