<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General on University of Michigan Fencing Club</title><link>https://www.um-fencing.com/categories/general/</link><description>Recent content in General on University of Michigan Fencing Club</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>(c) 2024 University of Michigan Fencing Club</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:49:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.um-fencing.com/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Donate</title><link>https://www.um-fencing.com/donate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:49:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.um-fencing.com/donate/</guid><description>The University of Michigan Fencing Club is excited about the upcoming season. We are not only eager to defend our title as the USACFC national champions, but we want everyone on campus to have the opportunity to join our club, learn how to fence, and take fencing with them for the rest of their lives.
One of our top priorities is investing in the future to create a growing and sustainable organization.</description></item><item><title>About Fencing</title><link>https://www.um-fencing.com/about_fencing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:07:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.um-fencing.com/about_fencing/</guid><description>The sport of fencing has three weapons: foil, epee and saber. The object of a fencing bout (what an individual &amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; is called) is to land a specified number of touches on your opponent before he/she scores that number on you. Each bout is officiated by a referee called a director.
Electric Scoring All official tournaments are conducted using electric scoring systems. The fencers connect themselves, their blades, and their metal jackets (lames) to a retractable cord (reel), which plugs in to a scoring machine (pictured left).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.um-fencing.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 15:09:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.um-fencing.com/contact/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you! If you have a question, you can ask any of our officers at practice or contact us electronically.
Have general inquiry questions? Email us at fencingofficers@umich.edu. We can help in person, too. Stop by during any practice and we&amp;rsquo;ll take care of you.Want to anonymously give feedback, ask a question, raise a concern, etc.? Please use our suggestions box.Officers Position Name Email Address Contact About Co-President Rachel Hendrian hendrian@umich.</description></item><item><title>Roster</title><link>https://www.um-fencing.com/roster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.um-fencing.com/roster/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s Team Name Weapon Year Hometown Zach Brooks Epee Grad Shawnee, KS Ian Chu (Captain) Epee SO Bozeman, MT Kyle Garcia-Rogers Epee SO North Reading, MA Robert Harter Epee JR Chesterfield, VA Keith Haw (Captain) Epee JR Pittsburgh, PA Aditya Kalahasti Epee FR Solon, OH Ryan Kersten Epee FR Ann Arbor, MI Sanil Mittal Epee SO New Delhi, India Ryan Moon Epee SO Johns Creek, GA Kaelan Mulye Epee FR Munising, MI Armando Otero Epee Non-Student San Juan, Puerto Rico Mitchell Schrank Epee Non-Student Wilmette, IL Colin Yoon Epee SR Larkspur, CA Alexander Ahn Foil Grad Los Angeles, CA Brandon Battle Foil SR Detroit, MI Michael Chen Foil FR Bloomfield Hills, MI Atticus Driver Foil JR Yuba City, CA Alexander Gordon Foil FR Hastings-on-Hudson, NY James Kennedy Foil SR Oak Park, IL Will Kuch Foil FR Frankenmuth, MI Nate Maceri Foil FR Macomb, MI Gordon Ng Foil SO Southgate, MI Aaron Renberg Foil Grad Bethesda, MD Cameron Rifkin Foil SR Birmingham, MI Martin Rodriguez Foil Grad Houston, TX Zhenyu Tan Foil Grad China Hasan Zengin Foil SO Istanbul, Turkey Akshat Arya Saber FR Troy, MI Thomas Choi Saber SR Lake Orion, MI Joshua Cooper Saber Grad Detroit, MI Craig Darnell Saber FR Lansing, MI Jake Huang Saber SR China Michael Mancuso Saber FR West Windsor, NJ Ian Moore Saber FR Clinton, NJ Sean Richards Saber JR Canton, MI James Utley Saber SR Canton, MI Jonathan Wang (Captain) Saber SO Troy, MI Nathaniel White Saber JR Concord, MA Yaodong Xin Saber Grad Qingdao, China Women&amp;rsquo;s Team Name Weapon Year Hometown Rachel Helen-Marie DeVeyra Epee FR Chicago, IL Vivian Fernandez (Captain) Epee Grad New York, NY Sookyung Heo Epee SR Seoul, South Korea Hilary Lam Epee JR Bloomfield Hills, MI Rebekah Yonghee Lim Epee Grad KS Sophia Lupton Epee FR New York, NY Brianna Moglianesi Epee SR Warren, NJ Sunskriti Paranjape Epee SR Portland, OR Jennifer Bhuiyan Foil FR New York, NY Ryan Ettner Foil SO Culver City, CA Rachel Hendrian (Captain) Foil JR Farmington Hills, MI Azaria Knight Foil SR Southfield, MI Eilene Koo Foil FR Ann Arbor, MI Prudence Russell Foil FR Edina, MN Dominika Urbaniak Foil SO Hamtramck, MI Lahari Vavilala Foil SR Novi, MI Chuqiao Wang Foil JR China Lucy Wang Foil SR Beijing, China Orlaith Fournier Saber SR Berkley, MI Ana Ha Saber JR Grand Rapids, MI Ami Hasebe Saber Grad Tokyo, Japan Sam Jiao Saber Grad Beijing, China Margaret Koberstein (Captain) Saber JR Libertyville, IL Emerson Lauster Saber SO Gaylord, MI Nga Chi Leong Saber FR Macao, China Petra Mihalko Saber SO Grosse Ile, MI Caroline Murphy-Racette Saber Grad Wellesley, MA Agamjot Sangotra Saber Grad Montgomery, NJ Sarah Squadrito Saber FR Bernardsville, NJ Michelle Wu Saber JR Ridgewood, NJ Michelle Xu Saber SR Novi, MI Xi Yuan Zheng Saber SO New York, NY Maria Zurbuchen Saber SO McLean, VA Coaches Name Position Ian Kanar Foil Coach Zach Brooks Epee &amp;amp; Foil Coach Jason Goodman Epee Coach Roland Kwok Epee Coach Michael Yee Sabre Coach</description></item></channel></rss>